[Praise]
255 No
Say
that Hello friends, my name is Sachi and
I welcome you to your own YouTube channel Wealth.
So friends, to
complete this, we will go through these five key
points which are return profile
and sales promoter holding, the most
important forecast in future of work.
After completing these children, we
will do contributions and recommendations and
here we will decide it.
From here, I have explained the reason in the video. There are some videos
which I should pay special attention to on my channel
like Udyog Industries, Top Ten Years,
Titan, D-Mart, Hero Industries, Paoge
Industries, Sterlite Industries and Asian
Paints. So, if you are interested in any video,
you can go to my channel and
check them out. Friends, in today's
video, we will talk about India
Limited. Talking about the company profile on Play Store,
you can see
that India is a healthcare company, games in
pharmaceutical plastics company, with a
portfolio of medium-low strips,
medical devices, nutritional facts and
genetic pharmaceuticals. See friends,
sector healthcare  This is Quantity Girls, the
last step company,
70 crores after leaving the market place and going to the office and Rahu Ketu is coming out,
if we talk about the cycle, then
you can see that the current price is more than
intensively, if we talk about speed gains vs
zombie, then the returns are much better, if we
talk about digital, then it is not so attractive,
although this year the president has
given more than last time, I will
tell you how much dividend has been given in the video
and if we talk about Interpol, then good
time to consider stockist Martin volume,
unmute flex Hindi stop, if you look at that girl, then
you can see that after getting the
sector copied, wash 33.5 and the stop which
is 157 75 is left, then 3.4 seven and if we
talk about the fourth generation, then 17.02 is coming out,
leaving this and talking about the rest, the
cent and stay will be tied at 24, which is also coming out
quite good, if we
talk about companies from behind this, then friends,
you can see Sun Pharma Tips, which is the
market leader of this sector and  Dr
Reddy's Laboratories and comes at number from the market side
and which is
not at number much behind About India,
after that if you can see then
its market price is much below 153 lut 5 6 7 4 inches, so if
you want you
can check it by comparing between them, by
pausing the video, right now medical
shop's playlist is on the next, if
from retail then light things friends you can see then
I have put edit cut such system
return activity is in five percent, whereas but
friend I have given a return of 20% positive
button if after one year time SIM here
you can see that it has given a strong return
that positive energy appointment 6.5
percent cut in stem cell, after this
in the members of peace, a21 will ask, a
great return of 29.58 percent if we talk about 10 years
then you can see here
Sanchet we have taken out, I have given 2.4 percent
less quantity in four digits
1310 75 East program any  If we look at the time,
we can see that the
award winnings have always given higher returns than the Parliament.
After the fans of the stock, we can see Chetak. From 2009 to 2019,
I got hurt. If we look at the net profit,
you can see that
we are seeing a rise here.
Without any moment, a lot of battery data is coming out. There is a
continuous increase in net flow.
If we talk about history, you can see here that from
2010 onwards, we
saw a decrease here. And after this, if we talk about it,
we are
seeing a rise again. There is only one, that too
in 2011, which is quite old. Okay, so we
can leave it mixed. It
brings a lot of battery savings. If we
talk about net profit, you can see that
here also the net profit is
seen in positive terms.
From here till here, you can see that the
net profit is continuously increasing.
In 2018, we have seen a net profit here
compared to 2017.  It was less visible and back
because in 2019 we reached the village road office so
friends if we
can keep the data of financial year 2017 then if we talk about total then
here I am getting the income from total
but if we talk about work then net
income is written here but if we talk about our tour then
here you can see
Anil is the person here, increase to
Ajay after that if we talk about mini statement then
friends you can see that the
revenue of last five years is coming out,
a 10.28 network industry
project 10.22 industry camera of this
which is to Praveen, if we talk about the market of every 5 years then
if we talk about the corporation of Sarpanch Sangh more than body and mind then you
can see here that this is the new version of the country for 5 years,
it comes out but less
time deposit but integration 1.00 is
less meeting as compared to the industry
so let's see so this is a very good thing in
this way you see friends so if we
talk about Krishna wedding pattern then you can see
if your  Near 76.09 station near the
setting rocky cliff in the court if we
talk about maximum then
friends time has gone inside the different if we
talk about the device then protein has been admitted in defense if we
talk about motor sweet recovery then the
report chapter limited has
rice is fine and
after the robbers relative interested is 5th
September most buildings
after that if it is December 2019 2020 and
master data computer then we can see
we found it inside mutual fund
and then the degree of that room was seen and
understand 1 minute increase and next we have seen
its price by
talking like this friends you can see that the national
medium was coming out that was 56.25
percent so at 56.25 its price was
in the project after 19 years it was
coming out cold and very low you can compare it to
4.9 percent so if the current price
is 1609 from here if it goes to 4.8 then we have to
press 1680 here  If
scientists decide to see this, then
I can get a certificate in the valley.
If I had seen it together with high, then
I can see a return of 12.5% ​​in quality.
After this, if you can see
this railway inquiry friends, here you
can see the shape of the last three years and the
gang of criminals, it was coming out to be
12.5%, that in 20 years in opposition to the selected
joint party president Sonia Gandhi, there can be a
decrease here. What is
important to do is
4.20 crore, then from there there is a rise of 7.50,
so you can see in point 2001,
if it was 4.30 crore in the last, if the
high Syed officer will see 100, then
friends, you can see that the
last one should be more than 28.93, whereas this
year you are seeing a decrease. Just
like the current share on the person, if we
see less than 10 cents from here, then I can get 28.70 this year because
look from above, and poor people  If it comes
out then it goes from 30473 only,
two-three it can be seen for 1508 minutes,
friends before moving ahead in the video let me
tell you do not forget to like and subscribe the video
so that in the same way
we are with you in the latest video, you can watch
friends ICC definition has given brother's rating
and given a target price of 19030 and if we
talk then CLSA has given a
rating of former on 20 minute pointed out and the target
price given is 1831, seventh if we consider it as
a year type
that it is beautiful there 2142 is bursting
and if we talk about 500 then the scientist is
661, it is being told that it is not meaningful, it has come out recently,
send this message,
he has cleared the new version of the
audit
product follow generator to award people with understanding, monitor and its
advanced version 2.2 has been launched this minute, the
cream of Audi has given this reference and it has been
launched at a very cheap price from the computer at a very low price and which
in the future it
This is going to help a lot in revenue generation, you can see
all this ad Kumar Jain infection relief
from battery, this finished goods and supplies
and activation, so this is a big reason, so
due to this we are seeing a decline in the stock here
and if we talk about it, it
started at 11.3, Satbir is at
₹2, the growth of my duty staff in the
office and power plant, so
basically in therapy and power plant, the
more guru we see, due to which we
saw a growth in the warrior here, so if I
talk clearly this year, then about
Om Guru track in power and celebrity
Arundhati, this point is this track record,
friends, if we talk about the last ten years, then
this company has given it and its growth is
234 percent, see here you
can see finally
wash the special dinner from Bigg Boss and then you
can see it friends and you can see
here you can see this, this is from this
and see here this, so if you
Bandhakar has done it till now with his brother
but this green government line that
is visible can give you an insult above 1579,
it supports around 15700,
so from 15800 to
15600 and in this range you can point inside it,
you can see once, its
day also came again, do this level and when if
you have to select it, it is above, if it is done then the
current price you have to follow is
at 1893, then the lantern is given on the graph,
so you cannot add it in it, if you
are a doctor, then if this stock is seen around 1893,
then you
can free the software by clicking on it and
with this we end the video, thank you
bye take care